i r ir ir
ir ir ir
i r ir ir ir ir ir
The skirt of the girl is dirty,
这个女孩儿的裙子很脏
so is her shirt.
她的衬衣也是
The skirt of the girl is dirty,
这个女孩儿的裙子很脏
so is her shirt.
她的衬衣也是
ir ir ir
f ir fir
冷杉
ir ir ir
s ir sir
先生
ir ir ir
f ir fir
冷杉
ir ir ir
s ir si
先生
Brown bear, brown bear,
棕熊  棕熊
have you seen a fir?
你见过一棵冷杉树吗
Yes, sir! Yes, sir!
当然了  先生  当然了  先生
Not far away from here.
离这儿不太远
Brown bear, brown bear,
棕熊  棕熊
have you seen a fir?
你见过一棵冷杉树吗
Yes, sir! Yes, sir!
当然了 先生  当然了  先生
Not far away from here.
离这儿不太远
ir ir ir
ir t irt
irt irt irt
sh irt shirt
衬衫
sk irt skirt
短裙
ir ir ir
ir t irt irt irt irt
sh irt shirt
衬衫
sk irt skirt
短裙
The girl in a pink skirt
穿粉色裙子的女孩儿
likes to twirl her skirt.
喜欢转裙子
The girl in a pink skirt
穿粉色裙子的女孩儿
likes to twirl her skirt.
喜欢转裙子